<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>secretmustache</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on secretmustache</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://m8ttyb.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Matt Brandt</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2022/writing_again/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2022/writing_again/</guid><description>whoami Considered by some a desert rat and dreamer who frequently escapes into the world for dad-like adventures. Professionally I am Software Engineer.
I recently joined Planet Labs, where the group has carved out a new role within the Platform Operations team - Operational Readiness Engineering.
I have a rich past working in Open Source; as a project maintainer and core contributor with IBM and Mozilla. The two and a half years between Mozilla and Planet were spent exploring Site Reliability engineering.</description></item><item><title>Matt Brandt</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/about/</guid><description>whoami Considered a desert rat and dreamer who frequently escapes into the world for dad-like adventures. Professionally I am Software Engineer, Program Manager, and Engineering Manager.
As part of a professional growth arc, I’ve moved into Reliability Engineering to understand the roles, impact, and how this domain elevates an engineering organization. I am currently the Lead Site Reliability Engineer for Firstup, working on EKS deployed microservices that service millions of requests per day.</description></item><item><title>Pingdom</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/pingdom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 09:36:44 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/pingdom/</guid><description>Monitoring The fourth quarter of 2015 for our team at Mozilla was a really great one. Across the group we had a well rounded list of goals supporting project initiatives as well as ones that were forward facing. Among the forward facing goals, a few of the areas included improving our code quality and the exploration of new techniques and technologies for assessing project health.
I personally gravitated towards the latter when I was considering a deliverable.</description></item><item><title>Boulder QA Meetup</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/boulder_qa_meetup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/boulder_qa_meetup/</guid><description>Boulder QA Meetup - Discussion on CD I recently visited with a group of software testers up in Boulder, Colorado to discuss peoples thought&amp;rsquo;s and feeling&amp;rsquo;s about Continuous Delivery. The trip highlighted that this conversation still covers unfamiliar ground among software developers and testers alike.
As a few of you are likely to acknowledge I have strong opinions on this subject. I purposely left my opinions at home, I wanted to observe the natural progression of the conversation among the group.</description></item><item><title>Make the intern do it</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/the_intern_io/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2015/the_intern_io/</guid><description>A shared experiment As a QA team we had a difficult and challenging quarter to end 2014 on; that said, the work with the MDN team was a personal highlight for me. A fulfilling way to cap off the end of the year.
The goal was to implement an experiment: convert several Python-based tests into JavaScript. Place these tests into the build process that the developers use and see what it nets.</description></item><item><title>Continuous Delivery Discussion</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/continous_delivery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/continous_delivery/</guid><description>Many of Mozilla’s web projects have adopted concepts from continuous delivery. Once a code change lands on a master branch it is shepherded to production with little-to-no human intervention. Quickly getting new features out to users.
While the implementation details vary from project to project, the core concepts tend to remain the same between projects. It is important for project stewards; project managers, developers, testers, UX, community, etc to have a shared vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Mozillians Vouch Refactor</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/mozillians-vouch-refactor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/mozillians-vouch-refactor/</guid><description>Mozillians Vouch Refactor - Testday Welcome to the Mozillians project. We love working with old and new contributors!
The latest feature set of the community phonebook has landed and is ready for testing. The phonebook is a place to find, share, and communicate with open web advocates throughout the world.
The community has worked to find creative ways to make the phonebook a place where active and trusted memebers of the community can connect.</description></item><item><title>Commtools Meetup</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/commtools_meetup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/commtools_meetup/</guid><description>The Mozilla Community Tools team is hosting a Meetup this week, June 10 - 12,
Prior to the Meetup the group brainstormed goals for the gathering as well as a loose schedule. Ongoing meeting notes can be found here. * If you would like to participate please ping us in #commtools. The Web QA group is giving a brief presentation on 2014-06-11: commtools_meetup_presentation.pdf</description></item><item><title>Java Posse Roundup - A winter trek</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/posse_roundup/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2014/posse_roundup/</guid><description>Open Space Conference By several orders of magnitude this year’s Java Posse Roundup was more interesting and engaging than the previous year. In large part due to my increased comfort attending an OpenSpace event, primarily, as a participant it is up to me to infuse energy into the event even when I am not a subject expert, let alone a novice on a topic.
I&amp;rsquo;ve learned to respect the law of two feet, to be a participant in each discussion I attend or leave and find a session that does interest me.</description></item><item><title>Reflections Footprints</title><link>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2013/reflections-footprints/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2013 19:36:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://m8ttyb.github.io/blog/2013/reflections-footprints/</guid><description>I am having a quiet evening tonight shuffling through imagery and thoughts of my past and wondering what is next. I didn&amp;rsquo;t sit down tonight with the intent to write this. It just felt right. This post is for me. Finally.
&amp;ldquo;He was a wanderer on a prehistoric earth, on an earth that wore the aspect of an unknown planet. But time is the fire in which we burn. We are but a fleeting moment, a footprint at the edge of the rising tide.</description></item></channel></rss>